Contact

demitria.stafford@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/demitriastafford-msn-rn-rn-bc-a46962144 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

nursing

Geriatric Nursing

Nursing Management

Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS) Certification

NIH Stroke Scale Certification
Medical Surgical Certification (RN-BC)

Basic Life Support (BLS)
Certification

National Incident Management System (NIMS) Certification

Demitria Stafford, MSN, RN, RN-BC

Doctor of Nursing Practice at Abilene Christian University Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Loyal, honest, and hardworking nurse manager who represent a leader, coach, and spokesperson for my fellow staff members by delivering and striving for the world class in patient care. I provide strong leadership skills for my team and strive for excellence in the overall care provided throughout the healthcare organization. Exemplary background of enhanced healthcare practices, skills, and focused abilities.

Clinical Experiences/Memberships

- Medication Administration
- Preceptor
- Telemetry Interpretation and Supervision
- Team Player and Leadership
- Great Personality and Hard worker
- Great Attendance Record
- Nursing Leadership and Advisory Co-chair
- Peer Review Board Member

Experience

HCA Healthcare Nurse Manager August 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months)

Tomball, Texas

Community Health Systems

13 years 6 months

Interim Manager

April 2017 - August 2017 (5 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Lead Charge Registered Nurse - Tomball Regional Medical Center

July 2014 - April 2017 (2 years 10 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Lead Charge Nurse, patient care, IV insertions, peer interviews, scheduling, leadership meetings, training and education, audits, leadership rounding, presentations, evaluations, and co-chair on nursing council.

Charge Registered Nurse - DeTar Hospital March 2004 - June 2014 (10 years 4 months)

Victoria, Texas Area

Charge Nurse, patient care (medications, wound care, assessments, computer charting, IV care/ insertion, foleys, PEG tube, vital signs, PCA, blood transfusions, etc..), preceptor, and nursing council member.

Education

Abilene Christian University

Doctor of Nursing Practice, Nursing (2019 - 2021)

The University of Texas at Arlington MSN, Nursing Administration w/ Certification in Nursing Education · (2017 - 2018)

The University of Texas at Arlington BSN, Nursing · (2015 - 2016)

Victoria College

RN, Associate of Applied Science, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (1997 - 2003)